

MOUSSA EL LAKKI iOS Developer

## CONTACT

- **Q** Sweden Malmö
- Moussa.Lakki@hotmail.com
- in linkedin.com/in/moussaellakki
- +46739612818
- GitHub
- Portfolio

# **SKILLS**

- Communication
- Problem-solving
- Teamwork
- Swift
- SwiftUI
- UIKit
- MVVM
- Swift Package Manager
- Core data
- Xcode
- Java
- Kotlin
- Firebase
- Git & Github
- API Networking
- UI/UX Design
- Figma

# LANGUAGES

- Swedish Fluent
- English Proficient
- Arabic Native

# Summary

Highly Skilled mobile application developer specializing in iOS. I started my career by learning programming at Folkuniversitetet in 2019. Since I started learning mobile development, I have developed and released three advanced apps to the App Store and Google Play. My portfolio showcases my work.

I am a quick learner and also a team player who loves writing code that is easy to read and manage. I also have good problem-solving skills, troubleshooting, and time management abilities.

# **EDUCATION**

# 2021-2022 MALMÖ YRKESHÖGSKOLA

Mobile App Development Program - Completed the Mobile App Development, focusing on native iOS and Android development.

#### 2020-2021 KOMVUX

Programming 2 - Completed the Programming 2 course with a focus on advanced object-oriented programming (OOP).

### 2019-2020 HERMODS

Programming 1 - Completed the Programming 1 course with a focus on basic object-oriented programming.

#### 2019-2020 FOLKUNIVERSITETET

Basic Programming - Completed the Basic Programming course

### 2007-2010 Malmö Folkhögskola

High School - Attended high school and received a diploma.

# **EXPERIENCE**

### 2021-2022 MALMÖ YRKESHÖGSKOLA

Projects - Developed and released three advanced mobile apps on the App Store and Google Play.

#### 2016-2019 TETRA PAK AB

Functional Tester - Worked as a functional and technical tester, mainly assembling and testing hardware to ensure proper functioning.

### **2010-2016 GFAB GLASTEAM AB**

Machine Operator - Cut custom glass products using computer-controlled cutting and shaping machinery.

### 2004-2007 GLASS DESIGN (BUSINESS FOUNDER/OWNER)

Business Founder/Owner - Ran a small business selling and fabricating custom glass products using in-house machinery.

### 2000-2004 EL GHOUL CO

Machine Operator - Operated cutting/shaping machines via PC panel to cut and shape glass to specific dimensions."